Thomas Chester "Chet" Edwards State Legislative papers, Inclusive: 1957-1991, Bulk: 1982-1990.
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- 70th Session, 1977-1990; 5
  - Correspondence, 1986-1987; 1
    - Pari-mutuel Gambling (5 of 6), 1987 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - Pari-mutuel Gambling (6 of 6), 1987 (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - Parks and Recreation, Local, 1987 (Box 136, Folder 4)
    - Parks and Wildlife, 1987 (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - Police and Fire, 1987 (Box 136, Folder 6)
    - Property, 1987 (Box 136, Folder 7)
    - Rivers, 1987 (Box 136, Folder 8)
    - Securities Law, 1987 June (Box 136, Folder 9)
    - Seat Belt/Helmet Laws (1 of 5), 1987 (Box 136, Folder 10)
    - Seat Belt/Helmet Laws (2 of 5), 1987 (Box 136, Folder 11)
    - Seat Belt/Helmet Laws (3 of 5), 1987 (Box 136, Folder 12)
    - Seat Belt/Helmet Laws (4 of 5), 1987 (Box 136, Folder 13)
    - Seat Belt/Helmet Laws (5 of 5), 1987 (Box 136, Folder 14)
    - Sign Ordinances/Outdoor Advertising, 1986 (Box 136, Folder 15)
    - Solid and Hazardous Waste, 1987 (Box 136, Folder 16)
    - State Employees, 1987 (Box 136, Folder 17)
    - Sunset Advisory Committee (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 136, Folder 18)
    - Sunset Advisory Committee (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 136, Folder 19)
    - Taxes, General, 1987 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Taxes, Ad Valorem, 1987 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Taxes, Gross Receipts, 1987 (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - Taxes, Insurance Premiums, 1987 (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Taxes, Profession Services (1 of 3), 1987 (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Taxes, Profession Services (2 of 3), 1987 (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - Taxes, Profession Services (3 of 3), 1987 (Box 137, Folder 7)
    - Texas Constitution Amendments, 1987 (Box 137, Folder 8)
    - Thank You’s/Congratulations (1 of 3), 1986-1987 (Box 137, Folder 9)
    - Thank You’s/Congratulations (2 of 3), 1986-1987 (Box 137, Folder 10)
    - Thank You’s/Congratulations (3 of 3), 1986-1987 (Box 137, Folder 11)
    - Thank You’s/Congratulations (1 of 4), 1987 (Box 137, Folder 12)
    - Thank You’s/Congratulations (2 of 4), 1987 (Box 137, Folder 13)
    - Thank You’s/Congratulations (3 of 4), 1987 (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Thank You’s/Congratulations (4 of 4), 1987 (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Tort Reform, General (1 of 5), 1987 (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Tort Reform, General (2 of 5), 1987 (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Tort Reform, General (3 of 5), 1987 (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Tort Reform, General (4 of 5), 1987 (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Tort Reform, General (5 of 5), 1987 (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - Tort Reform, Jury Trial (1 of 15), 1987 (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - Tort Reform, Jury Trial (2 of 15), 1987 (Box 138, Folder 9)
    - Tort Reform, Jury Trial (3 of 15), 1987 (Box 138, Folder 10)
    - Tort Reform, Jury Trial (4 of 15), 1987 (Box 138, Folder 11)
    - Tort Reform, Jury Trial (5 of 15), 1987 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Tort Reform, Jury Trial (6 of 15), 1987 (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - Tort Reform, Jury Trial (7 of 15), 1987 (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Tort Reform, Jury Trial (8 of 15), 1987 (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Tort Reform, Jury Trial (9 of 15), 1987 (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - Tort Reform, Jury Trial (10 of 15), 1987 (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - Tort Reform, Jury Trial (11 of 15), 1987 (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - Tort Reform, Jury Trial (12 of 15), 1987 (Box 139, Folder 8)
    - Tort Reform, Jury Trial (13 of 15), 1987 (Box 139, Folder 9)
    - Tort Reform, Jury Trial (14 of 15), 1987 (Box 139, Folder 10)
    - Tort Reform, Jury Trial (15 of 15), 1987 (Box 139, Folder 11)
    - Tort Reform, Lawyer Fees, 1987 (Box 139, Folder 12)
    - Tort Reform, Liability Insurance (1 of 6), 1987 (Box 139, Folder 13)
    - Tort Reform, Liability Insurance (2 of 6), 1987 (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Tort Reform, Liability Insurance (3 of 6), 1987 (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Tort Reform, Liability Insurance (4 of 6), 1987 (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Tort Reform, Liability Insurance (5 of 6), 1987 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Tort Reform, Liability Insurance (6 of 6), 1987 (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - Trade, 1987 (Box 140, Folder 6)
    - Transportation, Autos, 1987 (Box 140, Folder 7)
    - Trucking (1 of 10), 1987 (Box 140, Folder 8)
    - Trucking (2 of 10), 1987 (Box 140, Folder 9)
    - Trucking (3 of 10), 1987 (Box 140, Folder 10)
    - Trucking (4 of 10), 1987 (Box 140, Folder 11)
    - Trucking (5 of 10), 1987 (Box 140, Folder 12)
    - Trucking (6 of 10), 1987 (Box 140, Folder 13)
    - Trucking (7 of 10), 1987 (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - Trucking (8 of 10), 1987 (Box 141, Folder 2)
    - Trucking (9 of 10), 1987 (Box 141, Folder 3)
    - Trucking (10 of 10), 1987 (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - TV and Radio, 1987 (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - Unions, 1987 (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - Utilities, General, 1986-1987 (Box 141, Folder 7)
    - Utilities, Local Measured Service (1 of 2), 1986-1987 (Box 141, Folder 8)
    - Utilities, Local Measured Service (2 of 2), 1986-1987 (Box 141, Folder 9)
    - Various Bills, 1987 (Box 141, Folder 10)
    - Water (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 141, Folder 11)
    - Water (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 141, Folder 12)
    - Youth, 1987 (Box 141, Folder 13)
  - Senate Bills, 1981-1988; 2
    - Abortion: S.B. 167, 1986-1987 (Box 141, Folder 14)
    - Abortion: S.B. 167, 1987 (Box 141, Folder 15)
    - Abortion: S.B. 167 (1 of 2), 1987, undated (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - Abortion: S.B. 167 (2 of 2), 1987, undated (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - Absentee Voting by Disabled Voters: S.B. 512, 1987 (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - Absentee Voting Application: S.B. 1167, 1987 (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - Absentee Voting: S.B. 1166, 1987 (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - Agricultural Finance Authority: S.B. 1259, 1987 (Box 142, Folder 6)
    - Alcohol on Boats and Aircraft: S.B. 523, 1987 (Box 142, Folder 7)
    - All-Terrain Vehicle (ATV): S.B. 939 (1 of 3), 1987-1988 (Box 142, Folder 8)
    - All-Terrain Vehicle (ATV): S.B. 939 (2 of 3), 1987-1988 (Box 142, Folder 9)
    - All-Terrain Vehicle (ATV): S.B. 939 (3 of 3), 1987-1988 (Box 142, Folder 10)
    - All-Terrain Vehicle (ATV): S.B. 939 and Civil Action (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 142, Folder 11)
    - All-Terrain Vehicle (ATV): S.B. 939 and Civil Action (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 142, Folder 12)
    - Bills Killed By Edwards, 1987 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Campaign Finance: S.B. 465, 1987 (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Child-Care Facilities: S.B. 1162, 1987 (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Children-Related Legislative Recommendations, 1987 (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - Construction Corporation Dissolution: S.B. 1278, 1987 (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Construction Corporation Punishments: S.B. 1277, 1987 (Box 143, Folder 6)
    - Construction Safety: S.B. 1276-1279, 1987 (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - Construction Site Deaths: S.B. 1276, 1987 (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - Criminal Background Checks: S.B. 332, 1987 (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - Criminal Background Check Related Bills, 1987 (Box 143, Folder 10)
    - Criminal Bond Execution: S.B. 185, 1987 (Box 143, Folder 11)
    - Criminal Justice, Emergency Prison Legislation: S.B. 215, 1987 (Box 143, Folder 12)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Adult Probation Law, undated (Box 143, Folder 13)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Department of Corrections Bill Drafts, 1987 (Box 143, Folder 14)
    - Department of Human Services Sunset Bill: S.B. 298 (1 of 4), 1987-1988 (Box 143, Folder 15)
    - Department of Human Services Sunset Bill: S.B. 298 (2 of 4), 1987-1988 (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Department of Human Services Sunset Bill: S.B. 298 (3 of 4), 1987-1988 (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Department of Human Services Sunset Bill: S.B. 298 (4 of 4), 1987-1988 (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Department of Human Services Sunset Bill: S.B. 298 Tape Transcript, 1987 (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - DWI Blood Samples: S.B. 422, 1987 (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - DWI Offender Drug and Alcohol Counseling: S.B. 423 and H.B. 313, 1986-1987 (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Election Code, Campaign Finance: S.B. 465, 1987 (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - Election Code, Correcting and Conforming Bill: S.B. 280, 1987 (Box 144, Folder 8)
    - Election Code and Presidential Primary, Southern Legislative Conference (1 of 2), 1986-1988 (Box 144, Folder 9)
    - Election Code and Presidential Primary, Southern Legislative Conference (2 of 2), 1986-1988 (Box 144, Folder 10)
    - Election Code Recodification Conforming Bill: S.B. 280, 1987 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Election Polling Place Restrictions Removal: S.B. 884, 1982-1987 (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Election Workers Schedule: S.B. 205, 1987 (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Workload: S.B. 181, 1987 (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Fairfield Hospital District: S.B. 18 (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Fairfield Hospital District: S.B. 18 (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Firemen to Participate in Political Activities: S.B. 332, 1987 (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - Foreign Trade Zones: S.B. 1495, 1987 (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - Fraudulent Solicitations Law Enforcement Personnel: S.B. 427, 1987 (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - Good Samaritan Law: S.B. 237, 1987 (Box 145, Folder 10)
    - Grade Changes for Extracurricular Eligibility: S.B. 1430, 1985-1987 (Box 145, Folder 11)
    - Gubernatorial “Lame Duck” Appointments: S.B. 183, 1987 (Box 145, Folder 12)
    - Health, Board of Medical Examiners: S.B. 171 (1 of 2), 1985-1987 (Box 145, Folder 13)
    - Health, Board of Medical Examiners: S.B. 171 (2 of 2), 1985-1987 (Box 145, Folder 14)
    - Health, Board of Medical Examiners: S.B. 171 (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 145, Folder 15)
    - Health, Board of Medical Examiners: S.B. 171 (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Health, Board of Medical Examiners Review, 1987 (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Health, Board of Medical Examiners Emergency: S.B. 87, 1987 (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Health, Long-Term Care and Alzheimer’s: S.B. 1134 and 1371, 1987 (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - High Technology, Entire Session Package, 1987, undated (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - High Technology, Faculty Workloads, 1984-1987 (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - High Technology, Gifted Student Programs: S.B. 607, and Research Grants: S.B. 678, 1987, undated (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - High Technology, Higher Education Research Grants, Indirect Cost Recovery: S.B. 678, 1987, undated (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - High Technology, Minorities in Engineering, 1987, undated (Box 146, Folder 9)
    - High Technology, Permanent Research Funds: S.B. 775, 1987 (Box 146, Folder 10)
    - High Technology, Session Bills, undated (Box 146, Folder 11)
    - High Technology, Superconducting Supercollider (CSSJR 44 and HJR 88) and Texas National Research Laboratory Commission (CSSB 1105 and HB 1909), 1987 (Box 146, Folder 12)
    - High Technology, Technology Plan Development, 1982-1987 (Box 146, Folder 13)
    - Higher Education Research Grants: S.B. 678, 1987 (Box 146, Folder 14)
    - Higher Education Research Grants: S.B. 678, 1987-1988 (Box 146, Folder 15)
    - Human Services Sunset Review: S.B. 298, Analysis, 1987 (Box 146, Folder 16)
    - Intellectual Property: S.B. 777, 1987 (Box 146, Folder 17)
    - Intellectual Property: S.B. 778, 1987 (Box 146, Folder 18)
    - Intellectual Property: S.B. 777 and H.B. 1401, 1987 (Box 146, Folder 19)
    - Judicial Retirement System of Texas Plan One: S.B. 192 (H.B. 187), 1987 (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Lobbyist Prohibition: S.B. 197, 1987 (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Local Measured Service, Report to the 70th Legislature, 1987 (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Local Telephone Service: S.B. 1022, 1987 (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Low Bids Construction Safety: S.B. 1279, 1987 (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Medical Liens and Estate Recovery: S.B. 298 (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Medical Liens and Estate Recovery: S.B. 298 (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - Nursing Home Employee Criminal Background Checks: S.B. 200, 1987 (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - Nursing Home Employee Criminal Background Checks: S.B. 200 (1 of 3), 1987 (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - Nursing Home Employee Criminal Background Checks: S.B. 200 (2 of 3), 1987 (Box 147, Folder 10)
    - Nursing Home Employee Criminal Background Checks: S.B. 200 (3 of 3), 1987 (Box 147, Folder 11)
    - Permanent Research Funding, 1987 (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Political Contributions 30-Day Limit: S.B. 336, 1987 (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Potential Legislation, 1987 (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - Primary Elections Financing: S.B. 1427, 1987 (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Research Funding: S.B. 775, 1987 (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Session House and Senate Legislation, 1987, undated (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Solicitations in the Name of Police Officers: S.B. 382, 1987 (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Tax Exemptions for Disabled Veterans: S.B. 721, 1987 (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - Tax Rollback: S.B. 1087, 1987 (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - Teacher Appraisal System: S.B. 1088, 1987 (Box 148, Folder 10)
    - Teacher Jury Service Exemption: S.B. 685 and H.B. 358, 1987 (Box 148, Folder 11)
    - Telecommunications Carrier Regulations, Notes: S.B. 229, 1987 (Box 148, Folder 12)
    - Testimonies: S.B. 229, 1987 (Box 148, Folder 13)
    - Texas Conservation Foundation: S.B. 296, 1987 (Box 148, Folder 14)
    - Texas Department of Human Services: S.B. 298, 1987 (Box 148, Folder 15)
    - Texas National Research Laboratory Commission: S.B. 1535, 1987 (Box 148, Folder 16)
    - Tort Reform, S.B. 287 and Other Bills (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 148, Folder 17)
    - Tort Reform, S.B. 287 and Other Bills (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - Tort Reform Bills (1 of 2), 1987, undated (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - Tort Reform Bills (2 of 2), 1987, undated (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - Tort Reform Bills (1 of 2), undated (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - Tort Reform Bills (2 of 2), undated (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - Traffic Clean-Up: S.B. 1260, 1987 (Box 149, Folder 6)
    - TSTA Career Ladder: S.B. 772, 1987 (Box 149, Folder 7)
    - Tuition Discount Program, Public School Teacher Children: S.B. 214 (1 of 2), 1984-1987 (Box 149, Folder 8)
    - Tuition Discount Program, Public School Teacher Children: S.B. 214 (2 of 2), 1984-1987 (Box 149, Folder 9)
    - Utilities, Local Exchange Telecommunications Regulation: S.B. 444, 1987 (Box 149, Folder 10)
    - Utilities, Regulation of Telecommunication Carriers (1 of 2), 1987, undated (Box 149, Folder 11)
    - Utilities, Regulation of Telecommunication Carriers (2 of 2), 1987, undated (Box 149, Folder 12)
    - Utilities, Equal Regulation of Texas Long Distance Telecommunication: S.B. 229 and H.B. 468, 1987 March (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - Venture Capital Growth Fund: S.B. 1048, 1987 (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Voting Number Release: S.B. 204, 1987 (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - Women and Minorities in Engineering Education: S.B. 972, 1982-1987 (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - Women and Minorities in Engineering Education: S.B. 91, S.B. 182, 1981-1987 (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - Women and Minorities in Engineering Education: S.B. 91, S.B. 182, 1983-1987 (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Senate Resolutions, 1985-1987; 3
    - Corsicana State Home: S.C.R. 148, 1987 (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - Health, Long-Term Care and Alzheimer’s: S.C.R. 66, 75, 76, and 85, 1987 (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - High Technology, Agriculture Joint Resolutions and Notes (1 of 2), 1985-1987 (Box 150, Folder 9)
    - High Technology, Agriculture Joint Resolutions and Notes (2 of 2), 1985-1987 (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - High Technology, Texas Growth Fund: S.J.R. 10, 1987 (Box 150, Folder 11)
    - Local Measured Service: S.R. 454, undated (Box 150, Folder 12)
    - Minister Plenipotentiary for Trade and Commerce, Eaman Tang: S.R. 70, 1987 (Box 150, Folder 13)
    - Navarro County Constable, Abolishing the Office, 1987 (Box 150, Folder 14)
    - Potential Legislation, 1987 (Box 150, Folder 15)
    - Redistricting: S.J.R. 39, 1987 (Box 150, Folder 16)
    - Science and Technology Policy Resolution: S.R. 46, 1987 (Box 150, Folder 17)
    - Small Agricultural Business Financial Assistance: S.J.R. 49, 1987 (Box 150, Folder 18)
    - Tort Reform: S.J.R. 15, undated (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - House Bills, 1985-1990; 4
    - Agricultural Diversification Program: H.B. 1373 and S.B. 1258, 1987 (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - Agricultural Finance Authority: H.B. 1183, 1987 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Ballot Form: H.B. 2364, 1987 (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - Ballot Printers: H.B. 1857, 1987 (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - Baylor University Police Bill: H.B. 957, 1987 (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Candidate Filing Deadlines: H.B. 1853, 1987 (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - Campaign Contributions, Recall Elections: H.B. 1818 (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - Campaign Contributions, Recall Elections: H.B. 1818 (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - Canvassing, Special Election: H.B. 1861, 1987 (Box 151, Folder 10)
    - Child Abuse and Pornography, House Select Committee, 1986-1990 (Box 151, Folder 11)
    - Construction Safety: H.B. 662-668, 1986-1987 (Box 151, Folder 12)
    - Corporation or Labor Organization Contribution Prohibitions: H.B. 1818 (1 of 2), 1987 (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Corporation or Labor Organization Contribution Prohibitions: H.B. 1818 (2 of 2), 1987 (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - County Courts, McLennan County: H.B. 2551, 1987 (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - Credit Services Organizations Regulations: H.B. 742, 1987 (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - Criminal Mischief: H.B. 587, 1987 (Box 152, Folder 5)
    - Disclosures of Financial Institutions: H.B. 1632, 1987 (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - Education Bills, 1987 (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - Election Bills, 1987 (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - Election Expenses: H.B. 1858, 1987 (Box 152, Folder 9)
    - Election Omnibus Bills: H.B. 612 (1 of 4), 1987 (Box 152, Folder 10)
    - Election Omnibus Bills: H.B. 612 (2 of 4), 1987 (Box 152, Folder 11)
    - Election Omnibus Bills: H.B. 612 (3 of 4), 1987 (Box 152, Folder 12)
    - Election Omnibus Bills: H.B. 612 (4 of 4), 1987 (Box 152, Folder 13)
    - Election Results: H.B. 1854, 1987 (Box 152, Folder 14)
    - Electronic Voting Systems: H.B. 1412, 1987 (Box 152, Folder 15)
    - Emergency Service Fees: H.B. 1103, 1987 (Box 152, Folder 16)
    - Emergency Telephone Services: H.B. 1424, 1987 (Box 152, Folder 17)
    - Equity: H.B. 1402, 1987 (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - Foreign Sales: H.B. 1987 (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - Health, Board of Medical Examiners Physician Regulation: H.B. 2560, 1987 (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - Health, Long-Term Care and Alzheimer’s: H.B. 420, 1066, 1987 (Box 153, Folder 4)
    - High Technology, Agricultural Diversification: H.B. 49, 1987 July (Box 153, Folder 5)
    - High Technology, Department of Commerce: H.B. 4, 1986-1987 (Box 153, Folder 6)
    - High Technology, Department of Commerce: H.B. 4, 1987, undated (Box 153, Folder 7)
    - High Technology, Entire Session Package, undated (Box 153, Folder 8)
    - High Technology, National Center for Manufacturing Sciences: H.B. 1407, 1987 (Box 153, Folder 9)
    - High Technology, Permanent Research Funds: H.B. 2181, undated (Box 153, Folder 10)
    - High Technology, Session Bills, undated (Box 153, Folder 11)
    - Homestead Act: H.B. 2024, 1987 (Box 153, Folder 12)
    - Homestead Loans and Federal Tax Deduction: H.B. 2279, Analysis, 1987 (Box 153, Folder 13)
    - Judicial Retirement System Annuity: H.B. 187, 1987 (Box 153, Folder 14)
    - Liability in Tort of a Municipality: H.B. 132, 1987 (Box 153, Folder 15)
    - Liability of Volunteer Advocates: H.B. 201, 1987 (Box 153, Folder 16)
    - National Center for Manufacturing Sciences: H.B. 1407, 1987 (Box 153, Folder 17)
    - Nominees on Ballot: H.B. 1852, 1987 (Box 153, Folder 18)
    - Petition Signature Numbers: H.B. 2276, 1987 (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - Polling Place Notices: H.B. 50, 1987 (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Potential Legislation, 1987 (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - Precinct Convention Records Disposition: H.B. 2370, 1987 (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Property Tax Bill: H.B. 1281, 1987 (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - Regulation Securities and Fees: H.B. 875, 1987 (Box 154, Folder 6)
    - Sales and Use Tax: H.B. 2559, 1987 (Box 154, Folder 7)
    - School District Boundaries: H.B. 1617, 1987 (Box 154, Folder 8)
    - Street Cleaning License: H.B. 58, 1987 (Box 154, Folder 9)
    - Sunset Omnibus Bill: H.B. 2243, 1987 (Box 154, Folder 10)
    - Teacher Retirement System: H.B. 2623, 1987 (Box 154, Folder 11)
    - Voter Registration Application: H.B. 613, 1987 (Box 154, Folder 12)
    - Voting Booths: H.B. 1851, 1987 (Box 154, Folder 13)
    - Women and Minorities in Engineering Education: H.B. 102, 1985-1987 (Box 154, Folder 14)
  - House Resolutions, 1985-1987; 5
    - Antiquities Study: H.C.R. 66, 1987 (Box 154, Folder 15)
    - Health, Long-Term Care and Alzheimer’s: H.C.R. 25, 98, 99, 1987 (Box 154, Folder 16)
    - High Technology, Superconducting Supercollider: H.C.R. 53, 1985-1987 (Box 154, Folder 17)
    - High Technology, Superconducting Supercollider Facility: H.J.R. 88, 1987 (Box 154, Folder 18)
    - Potential Legislation, 1987 (Box 154, Folder 19)
    - Small Agricultural Business Financial Assistance: H.J.R. 58, 1987 (Box 154, Folder 20)
  - Topical, 1977-1990; 6
    - Agriculture, 1987 (Box 154, Folder 21)
    - Agriculture Crime Fund, 1987-1988 (Box 154, Folder 22)
    - AIDS Legislative Task Force, 1987 (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - Alzheimer’s Disease, Session Legislation and Research, 1987, undated (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Arts Commission, 1987 (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - Arts in Corsicana, 1987 (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Budget, 1987 (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - Appropriations Conference Committee Report, 1987 (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Business, Position Statement, 1987 (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - Child Care, 1987 (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - Construction Safety, Articles, 1986-1987 (Box 155, Folder 9)
    - Corsicana, 1987 (Box 155, Folder 10)
    - Criminal Justice, 1987 (Box 155, Folder 11)
    - Criminal Justice, Board of Pardons, Summary of Public Testimony, undated (Box 155, Folder 12)
    - Criminal Justice, Criminal Justice Biennial Legislature Report, 1987 (Box 155, Folder 13)
    - Criminal Justice, Crime Victim Newsletters, 1985-1986 (Box 155, Folder 14)
    - Criminal Justice, Emergency Funding Ruiz Compliance, 1987 (Box 155, Folder 15)
    - Criminal Justice, General, 1984-1986 (Box 155, Folder 16)
    - Criminal Justice, Recidivism, 1985-1987 (Box 155, Folder 17)
    - Criminal Justice, Sunset Advisory Commission, Combination and Diversion Alternatives, 1986-1987 (Box 155, Folder 18)
    - Criminal Justice, Sunset Advisory Commission, Combination and Diversion Alternatives, 1986, undated (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Criminal Justice, Sunset Staff Evaluation (1 of 2), undated (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Criminal Justice, Sunset Staff Evaluation (2 of 2), undated (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Adult Probation Commission, Board of Pardons Statistical Reports, 1984-1986 (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Adult Probation Commission, Code of Criminal Procedure Clean-Up, undated (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Adult Probation Commission, Sunset Interest Group Meeting Notes, undated (Box 156, Folder 6)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Adult Probation Commission, Sunset Recommendations Comments, 1986 (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Adult Probation Commission Board of Pardons, 1986 (Box 156, Folder 8)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Adult Probation Commission notes, 1987 (Box 156, Folder 9)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Crime Poll Summary Report, 1986 (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Department of Corrections, Alcohol and Drug Abuse, 1985-1987 (Box 156, Folder 11)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Department of Corrections, Alcohol and Drug Abuse, Information and Speech, 1987 (Box 156, Folder 12)
    - Criminal Justice, Texas Department of Corrections, Mental Health and Mental Retardation — Mentally Retarded Inmates, 1985-1987 (Box 156, Folder 13)